Hello Anil, my friends,
welcome to my YouTube channel Surat Clinic.
In the last video, we talked about
how we can get a discount on our health insurance premium. So today we will
talk about that topic. I wo
n't tell you about what health insurance is, but I am very interested in one thing,
that even now only 30 to
40% of people in India are aware about health insurance. The
remaining 60% of people do
n't have complete information about it and are not able to avail its benefits.
So friends, I have given the
entire video of health insurance
in the description box, you
can check it from there. But today's
video is about discounts. I am going to
tell you five such ways, friends, through which
you can get a discount on PM.
My name is Aakhir Singh Rawat.
Welcome to my kitchen showroom plane.
Friends, if you haven't subscribed to my channel yet,
please subscribe to Palace
and press the bell icon
so that you don't have to go to Palace in the market for health insurance, motor
insurance, life insurance for
investment.
Okay, friends, let's get started.  This is the
first way to get a record,
if you are a single man, just an individual
single player, only for yourself and on the other hand there is
a plan, this is called a family floater plan, if you
definitely go for a family floater plan, then
we get a discount on it,
like the name of Vidhi Insurance Company,
once you send it, your 5 lakh
sum comes to Rs.8000 individual, but if
you add your bike and children in it, then
its premium will be Rs.11,000 to 13,000, that is, it will
not be like this, why will it
double, the result will be Rs.11000, so
friends, if the term plan is changed, then this is the first
record, friends, there are many
people who are not aware about this,
but our job is to give them all this
information, let's move towards another topic,
now let's talk
about the other method of water, yes friends, if you
feel like your experiment, when Laxman
ji, your PM comes to Rs.8000 or
any big amount, a glance of it comes, then there are
many companies which if you  If you
pay a premium of two or three years, then
you get a discount of at least 10 to
14% of your preferred premium. It is
not that every company will
give discounts as per your wish. If the
company works on your sum
insured, it varifies that it is charging
minimum amount towards you. In the same, you get a
discount of up to 12, 14, 10%
if you use it for two or three years together. So,
friends, this is the second method.
Now we will talk about the third method. To
understand the third method, pay a little
attention. Try to understand the complaint. In
this method, we get two benefits.
If we have taken any insurance and we have
not made any claim in it yet, then
we get two benefits in it. First,
either your time limit increases automatically, that is, if
you have taken insurance of Rs 5 lakh, then in the
coming time, the sum assured can be Rs
7.5 lakh or ₹1000000.
So, this is one benefit. The second benefit is
this.  The answer is if you take a no claim bonus then it gives
you pimples now this
computer company varies whether it
gives it or not but you will definitely get one thing from both so
friends this is the
third method if you have come then you are on one
side to know about the fifth method in
which it gives you up to 50% and
before that let's talk about the fourth method let's talk
about the fourth method
it is called network discount
insurance company now you
also get discount from Parvati and Dengue this
insurance company also does the Dow company,
their chain Dow company varies, in the year in which they are connected with such lines
you can get discount there
friends okay so we have four
methods now let's talk about the fifth method so
friends let's talk about the fifth method
I am sure and that you are very
excited to know how can you get up to 50%
assistant friends this
point is called salary discount
increase what does it mean every
insurance company offers you to
download a help of the same company in your phone and how is the help that you can get a
discount  4000 chapter notes clearly, you are getting
updates, how many calories you do
not have to lock in the cord,
you should try that application yourself
or if you wear a smart watch then
you can attach it to it, like
you can keep it on the ball, you
can do that, so the thing is that your health
insurance will keep getting updated in it and
when the time for your premium comes,
then who will pay it in it,
understand this, for example, if you have taken an individual policy from one person,
your pimples are taken care of,
now you have
fixed a target for the wellness one, then the
premium that you will have to pay in this will be
around Rs.10000 or if
you have done all the work, then if you have taken an Alibaba, then
if you have taken a family floater plan, then
both the husband and wife will have to follow this, only then
you will be able to get the scan, so
you can ask your lifting,
how to download the verification,
how it works, so this thing will be of great
benefit to you friends  So these are the
external ways to get the record, there is also a desire method
which is not medical, I have
told you about special points, Chatterjee has women, the
real thing is that if women take health insurance and if they go
with their husband then they
get a discount, it comes
under the product line, so if
you feel that I am not telling you then I
hope you must have liked this topic,
I told you a lot about the test of health insurance,
if you have any
question then definitely ask in the comment box
and wait for my next video, in this
I will treat you and my next video also,
in the next video I am going to bring you
how you can
earn 40 thousand rupees a year and get
double the amount almost double the amount in six years,
and one option and meeting in
it is the return of 15 years and one option will be kept
for questions, in that you will
get 15000 sanskar return, friends,
you must watch this plan and mine too and
friends, you must like this video of mine
and clear the next video calling 2 to
3  I am going to come with that video within a minute. I
hope friends, you must have liked it
and you must also like my videos.
If so, then please do subscribe to my channel. Till then, bye,
see you in the next video. Thank you
friends.